{
    "question": "Soal : all these year , Dina's family.......... in poverty    a. has lived\u00a0\r\nb. was living\u00a0\r\nc. lives\u00a0\r\nd. has been living\r\ne. lived\u00a0\r\n\r\ntolong sertai dengan penjelasan ya",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "yang bener jawaban D kalo menurutku. Itu termasuk kalimat Present Perfect Continuous Tense yang rumusnya S + have/has + been + Ving. Tujuan teks itu adalah untuk menyatakan suatu kegiatan yang dimulai pada waktu lampau tetapi masih berlangsung sampai sekarang bahkan ada kemungkinan akan terus berlangsung. Clue nya itu phrase \"All these years\"<br><br>menurutku sih begitu\u00a0",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "buatlah-contoh-pecakapan-bahasa-inggris-tentang-pemesanan-meja-di-618",
            "question": "Buatlah contoh pecakapan bahasa inggris tentang pemesanan meja di restoran..",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "A: i want to ask permission<br>B: yes of course<br>A: two days there will be an event in my home, can i order 2 pieces of table<br>B: of course may be happy<br>A: ok i&#039;ll wait for tomorrow<br>B: okay, thank you&#039;ve booked a table here<br>A: you&#039;re welcome<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<span>A: Good afternoon <br>b: Good afternoon, can I help you? <br>A: I would like to reserve a table, for tomorrow afternoon? <br>b: yes, it could. for how many people? <br>A: I would like to reserve a table for lunch two people! <br>B: Yes sir, tomorrow daytime table number five <br>A: Thank you<span>.</span></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "definisi-positive-adjective-itu-apa-dan-contohnya-569",
            "question": "Definisi positive adjective itu apa ?? dan contohnya ???",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Definisi nya sudah diterangkan oleh mbak Karina, Yaitu berfungsi untuk menambahkan keterangan kata benda (noun),\u00a0 saya menambahkan contohnya saja <br><br>He has beautiful garden = adjective -&gt; beautiful noun nya garden<br><br>He has sharp eyes = adjective -&gt; sharp dari noun eyes<br><br>He loves to paint beautiful home -&gt; adjective beautiful dari noun home <br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "coba-sebeutkan-contoh-dari-spoof-dan-kesimpulannya-845",
            "question": "Coba sebeutkan contoh dari spoof dan kesimpulannya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Contoh :<br>Joe&#039;s Mother got angry because her son got a low mark on English test.<br>\n\"Why did you get such a low mark on that test?\" Asked mother angrily. \nAsked by his angry mother, Joe just kept silent and went out.<br>\nA few moment, Joe came back home and met his mother again. His mother asked the same question.<br>\nJoe answered steadily, \"Because of absence.\"<br>\n\"You mean you were absent on the day of the test?\" Mother wondered.<br>\nJoe replied, \"No, but the kid who sits next to me was.\"\n\n<br><br>Kesimpulan :<br><span><span>sebuah teks yang berisi tentang humor meski sebagian teksnya \nsudah dimodifikasi dari aslinya.</span></span><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bagaima-membalas-surat-kepada-pembeli-tersebut-kiara-agusta-jal-156",
            "question": "Bagaima membalas surat kepada pembeli tersebut??    kiara agusta\r\njalan W.Z Johanes No. 621\r\nThe Tiny Tots Toy Company\r\nJalan Kuningan Sari No. 50, Jakarta\r\nDear Costumer Service Respresentative,\r\n\r\nI recently purchased one of your Tiny Tents (Model #47485) for my three-year old daughter. Unfortunately, after viewing the components that came with the product, I discovered that four of the parts were missing. Also, the instructions that came with the tent are in portuguese and Russian, but not in english or french, the two languages I speak. These two unforeseen problems have resulted in the tent remeaning unassembled and unacceptable as a toy my daughter.\r\nI am writing to request replacements for the missing parts, and a copy of the full set of assembly instructions (in english or french) for the model I purchased. If reasonable arrangements are not made within ten bussines days, I will return the tent to the store I purchased it from and expect a full refund. To assist you in processing my request, I am including a copy of my sales receipt and a list of the missing parts.\r\nI have purchased other toys manufactured by your company in the past, and have always been impressed with the quality and selection that Tiny Tots has made available to its customers. I sincerely hope this is a one-time incident, and that any future purchases I make will live up to the standard my family has come to expect from your company.\r\n\r\nSincerely,\r\nKiara Agusta",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Dear Kiara Agusta,<br><br>I am glad that you let us know about this matter. We are more than happy to assist you and would like to keep you impress with our service. We apologize for the missing part of the screw which supposed to be attached to the tents. We will send it tomorrow. And also the copy of the instruction will be delivered together with these missing parts. Hopefully you are satisfied with our reply and always be our loyal customer<br><br>Regards<br><br>Toytots Representative<br>Laura <br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-recount-teks-tentang-stady-tour-di-jakarta-245",
            "question": "Contoh recount teks tentang stady tour di jakarta",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Saya hanya memberikan langkah pentingnya saja. Sebenarnya mudah untuk membuat recoun text. Topiknya kan, tentang study tour, coba cari informasi sejelas-jelasnya tentang study tour. Lalu, kembangkan menjadi sebuah recount teks. Pakai bahasa indonesia dulu. Setelah ditata rapi dengan bahasa indonesia yang baik dan literer, diubah ke dalam bahasa inggris. Okay ? @Liwed",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Aku kasih caranya aja ya. Pertama rangkai kejadian study tour kamu dari awal sampai akhir kemudian translate kan ke bahasa inggris, karena inti dari recount text itu menulis dan mengarang kejadian yang memang pernah terjadi dan kita alami<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "change-into-the-correct-simple-present-or-simple-past-form-1-i-897",
            "question": "change into the correct simple present or simple past form 1. I.....(live) right off an alleyway blablabla.. 2. It....(be) the alleyway behind blabla.. 3. this....(need) to be paid attention immediately and 4. ...... (require)immediate repairing. 5. blabla.. last night it ..... (rain) for maybe an hour, and look what it 6. ...... (do). 7. some of the potholes ..... (be) 5 inches deep. 8. please I .... (beg) you, blabla.. 9. we .... (need) the road resurfaced.\u00a0 10. it....(look) like a thrid world country outside my house. \u00a0 \u00a0 1. every day I .... (pass) rotan street to go to my office which it situated on burton street and 2. ..... (return) home the same route. this has been a routin for twelve years. but last week, to my dismay, I 3. .... (have) to go around to the other way when I 4. ...(return) home from my office. as I was going to turn to Rotan street, there 15. .... (be) a sign that all street users to rotan sreet 16. ... (can) enter it that day because one of the residentswas having a weeding party. 17. .... (have) to turn my car to pasadena street and I was trapped in a trafic jam half an hour. it 18. .... (be) a nuisance. I ..... (reach) home late in the evening. I think that streets 20..... (be) \u00a0for public use. it should not be use for private use. if you 21. ....(hold) a weeding party, you should rent a weeding hall or a meeting hall in the near sub district. streets 22 .... (be) for trafic, it \u00a023. .... (be) not for private party.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. lived<br>2.was<br>3.needed<br>4.required<br>5.rained<br>6.did<br>7.were<br>8.begged<br>9.needed<br>10.looked",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<span>\n                change into the correct simple present or simple past form\n1.\n                <span>change into the correct simple present or simple past form\n<br>1. I..LIVE...(live) right off an alleyway blablabla..\n<br>2. It...IS...(be) the alleyway behind blabla..\n<br>3. this..NEEDS..(need) to be paid attention immediately and <br>4. ..REQUIRES.... (require)immediate repairing.\n<br>5. blabla.. last night it ..RAINED... (rain) for maybe an hour, and look what it <br>6. ...DOES... (do).\n<br>7. some of the potholes ..ARE... (be) 5 inches deep.\n<br>8. please I .BEG... (beg) you, blabla..\n<br>9. we ..NEED.. (need) the road resurfaced.\u00a0\n<br>10. it..LOOKS..(look) like a thrid world country outside my house.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0\n<span><br><br>1. every day I ..PASS.. (pass) rotan street to go to my office which it \nsituated on burton street and 2. .RETURN.... (return) home the same route. \nthis has been a routin for twelve years. but last week, to my dismay, I \n3. HAD.... (have) to go around to the other way when I 4. .RETURNED..(return) home \nfrom my office. as I was going to turn to Rotan street, there 15. .WAS... \n(be) a sign that all street users to rotan sreet 16. ..COULDN&#039;T. (can) enter it \nthat day because one of the residents was having a weeding party. 17. \n.I HAD... (have) to turn my car to pasadena street and I was trapped in a \ntrafic jam half an hour. it 18. .WAS... (be) a nuisance. I ..REACHED... (reach) \nhome late in the evening. I think that streets 20...ARE.. (be) \u00a0for public \nuse. it should not be use for private use. if you 21. WILL HOLD....(hold) a \nweeding party, you should rent a weeding hall or a meeting hall in the \nnear sub district. streets 22 .ARE... (be) for trafic, it \u00a023. IS.... (be) \nnot for private party.</span></span>\n            </span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-beda-auxilary-amp-operator-siapa-penemu-font-old-english-907",
            "question": "-Apa beda Auxilary &amp; Operator?    -Siapa penemu font Old English?\r\n -Kapan Bahasa Inggris masuk ke Indonesia?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "gaktau ee kak bntar takcarikan yha<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-certia-bahasa-inggris-last-vocation-892",
            "question": "Contoh certia bahasa inggris \"last vocation\"",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "It&#039;s curious as we grow older, how easy it is to lose our sense of \ndirection, a sense of vocation, a sense of God&#039;s calling us to important\n things still to be done. Vocations are not just for the young starting \nout in marriage, a career, or religious life. There&#039;s another kind of \nvocation \u2014 a kind of \"late vocation\" \u2014 God&#039;s final call to a strong \nfinish. It is God&#039;s call to each one of us to grow old gracefully \u2014 full\n of grace \u2014 to grow toward Him.    \nGod calls us to respond heroically, like Saint Paul, pouring ourselves \nout like a libation until we can say: \"I have fought the good fight, I \nhave finished the race, I have kept the faith\" (II Tm 7).<span><br><br><br>INI</span>\u00a0?\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "combine-the-sentences-using-too-so-or-either-and-neither-1-d-745",
            "question": "Combine the sentences using : Too, so, or either and neither    1. Dogs\u00a0can't eat vegetables. Cats can't eat vegetables\r\n2. We haven't eaten yet. Father hasn't yet\r\n3. Mitha is not seventeen years old. I am not seventeen years old\r\n\r\nJawabannya yang Jelas ya :)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. Dogs can&#039;t eat vegetables. Neither can cats<br>2. We haven&#039;t eaten yet. Father hasn&#039;t either<br>3. Mitha is not seventeen years old. I am not either<br><br>setau aku begitu aja sih udah betul. mudah-mudahan membantu ya:)",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bagaimanakah-penggunaan-kata-either-720",
            "question": "Bagaimanakah penggunaan kata 'either'?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>untuk 2 kalimat yang sama-sama negative (-). Contoh dengan<span> (tenses 1) simple present tense, menggunakan </span></span><span><span>katakerja be (am, are is) dengan </span>katasifat (adjective) fine /fain/ = baik.</span><br>example:<br>you are not fine and i am not, either<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "untuk 2 kalimat sama-sama negative dengan menggunakan kata kerja be(am,are,is)<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}